<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.keysmith</id>
  <name>Keysmith</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Keysmith</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Keysmith</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Keysmith</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Keysmith</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Keysmith</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKeysmithxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Keysmith</name>
  <summary>A short summary describing what this software is about</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un breu resum descrivint de què tracta aquest programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een korte samenvatting die beschrijft waar deze software over gaat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um breve resumo que descreve para que serve esta aplicação</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Короткий опис призначення цього програмного забезпечення</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA short summary describing what this software is aboutxx</summary>
  <metadata_license>A permissive license for this metadata, e.g. "FSFAP"</metadata_license>
  <project_license>The license of this software as SPDX string, e.g. "GPL-3+"</project_license>
  <developer_name>The software vendor name, e.g. "ACME Corporation"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">El nom del venedor de programari, p. ex., «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">De leveranciersnaam van de software, bijv. "ACME Corporation"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">O nome do criador da aplicação, p.ex. "Empresa XPTO"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Назва розробника програмного забезпечення, наприклад «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxThe software vendor name, e.g. "ACME Corporation"xx</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>Multiple paragraphs of long description, describing this software component.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Múltiples paràgrafs de descripció llarga, descrivint aquest component de programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Meerdere paragrafen van lange beschrijvingen, die deze softwarecomponent beschrijven.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Diversos parágrafos de uma longa descrição, descrevendo o componente da aplicação.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Декілька абзаців повного опису цього компонента програмного забезпечення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMultiple paragraphs of long description, describing this software component.xx</p>
    <p>You can also use ordered and unordered lists:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">També podeu emprar llistes ordenades i sense ordenar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U kunt ook geordende en ongeordende lijsten gebruiken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Também poderá usar listas ordenadas ou não-ordenadas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ви можете використовувати упорядковані і неупорядковані списки:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxYou can also use ordered and unordered lists:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Feature 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Característica 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Vlastnost 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Functie 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidade 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFeature 1xx</li>
      <li>Feature 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Característica 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Vlastnost 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Functie 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidade 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFeature 2xx</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Keep in mind to XML-escape characters, and that this is not HTML markup.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Tingueu en compte els caràcters d'escapament en XML i que no està en un marcatge en HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Houd rekening met XML-escape tekens en dat dit geen HTML-opmaak is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Lembre-se de usar os caracteres de escape do XML e de que isto não está formatado em HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Слід пам'ятати, що символи XML слід екранувати, і що це не зовсім розмітка HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKeep in mind to XML-escape characters, and that this is not HTML markup.xx</p>
  </description>
</component>
